# **YURIY KOSHYK**

With 5+ years of experience, I combine design and technical expertise to create impactful digital experiences focusing on business and user needs. As a generalist in multiple domains, I always try to find the right unique approach for every specific case.

Outside of work, I enjoy movies, books, playing basketball, and doing street photography.

Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg, DE

yuriykoshyk.com linkedin.com/in/yuriy-koshyk yuriy.koshyk@gmail.com +380974399377

### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

APOLLO.IO [ B2B, AI, Sales, Enterprise, Web, SaaS ]

Role: Senior Product Designer

Go-to-market platform for sales and marketing teams to find and engage leads.

WORKRAMP [ B2B, EduTech, Enterprise, AI, LMS, SaaS ]

Role: Senior Product Designer

All-in-one learning platform for employee training, onboarding, and enablement.

**EVENTPOS** [B2B2C, Fintech, Entertainment, IOS, Android, Mobile SaaS]

Role: Product Designer

Award winning mobile payment solution specifically designed for events.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER**

KOSH | Freelance | Mar 2020 - Present

- Delivered 15+ projects, focusing on UX/UI design to drive business growth and user satisfaction;
- · Led full design research cycles, including user research, prototyping, and usability testing;
- $\cdot$  Created high-performance digital products aligned with business metrics;
- · Monitored KPIs to optimise designs based on user feedback and data-driven insights.

#### **HEAD OF SYSTEMS & IT (CTO)**

DF Druckluft-Fachhandel GmbH | Full-time | Aug 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Led the tech side of a multi-million dollar e-commerce company;
- · Increased company revenue by 10% in first months with optimization of UX and system processes;
- · Effectively managed internal cross-functional team + 4 external partner companies;
- · Implemented the Agile methodology in the majority of the departments;

#### **UX/UI DESIGNER & DEVELOPER**

Heimdal Data ApS | Full-time | Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

- · Adhered to design standards and collaborate with stakeholders;
- · Developed user-friendly interfaces with a focus on user experience;
- · Wrote clean and scalable code that increased product performance;
- $\cdot\,$  Conduct user research and gather requirements for the design process;
- · Brought creative design trends and new technologies to the company's projects.

#### **PRINCIPLES**

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Design Systems

Prototyping

Material Design

Human-Centered Design

Heuristic evaluation

**Product Thinking** 

Usability Testing & A/B Testing

User Research

#### **TOOLS**

Figma, ProtoPie, Hotjar

Adobe Creative Suite, Blender, Rive
Google Analytics, PowerBI, SQL

HTML5, CSS3, SASS

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js
GSAP, Famer Motion, Tailwind

Webflow, Framer, Prismic

#### **AWARDS**

The Best Android and IOS App Designs
Best Design Awards by DesignRush

Best Innovation and Creativity
Big Pitch Competition

#### **EDUCATION**



UX Design Medium
Projector Institute



Frontend Developer
IT School GolT



Media Communications Diploma

Humber College



Foundation in Computing Bournemouth University International College